Now I'm here at the Honor flagship store in London Waterloo and there's so much to see
I'll take some time and have a look around.
So I found quite some items and it's time to get changed now and try everything on.
Shine your light on me.
Illuminate me.
Make me complete.
Lay me down.
And wash this world from me.
Open the skies.
And burn it all away
Cause I've been waiting
All my life just waiting
For you to shine
Shine your light on me
I dreamt the world with my eyes open
But time moved on and then
New worlds begin again
Oh my heart
In this universe so vast
No moment was made to last
So light the fire in me
Shine, shine your light on me
Illuminate me
Make me complete
My dress is the Celine Knox dress on display here in the Honor Boutique.
So cool!